<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?>
<fomod>
	<Name>MiC - Make it Compatible</Name>
	<Author>Heromaster</Author>
	<Version MachineVersion="1.0">1.2.1</Version>
	<Description>Welcome to MIC - Make it compatible

This will be a series of selected mods which will be made compatible with Devious Devices - Assets and Devious Devices - Captured Dreamshop and also will be made compatible with each other so that you don't find yourself in a situation where you could put two different nipple piercings on your character, for example.

The items in this mod series will be made compatible to the following mods:
    * Devious Devices
    * Cloaks of Skyrim and Winter is Coming - Cloaks
    * Frostfall
    * Left Hand Rings


Calypsia - The Adult Toys Merchant
http://www.nexusmods.com/skyrim/mods/24421

Installation
It's fully integrated. No separte download necessary.

Changes
    * Fixed the keywords for all items (Removed ClothingHand, ClothingFeet, ClothingCirclet keywords and also JewelryExpensive keyword if the base value of that item was lower than 100 gold)
    * Fixed the detection sound values (Set it to 0 instead of 76)
    * Cat and pig ears now use the circlet slot
    * Seat of the Queen now uses slot 44 and 50 (matching the slot numbers of DD - Assets Gag Straps and Gag Mouthpiece)
    * Strapon's now use slot 48,49 and 54 (matching the slot numbers of DD - Assets Plug (Anal), Plug (Vaginal) and Chastity Belt)
    * Nipple pasties now uses slot 56 (matching the slot number of DD - Assets Chastity Bra)
    * Butt plugs now use slot 48 (matching the slot number of DD - Assets Plug (Anal)
    * Vaginal plugs now use slot 54 (matching the slot number of DD - Assets Plug (Vaginal)


SED7 Accessoire Piercingset for CBBE
http://www.nexusmods.com/skyrim/mods/20655

Installation
Install SED7 Piercingset first. You don't need to install the Allin1 Hotfix. After installing, deactivate the esp's.

Changes
    * Now does need SexLab as hard dependency
    * Merged the different *.esp's into a single one
    * Removed the Nipplewand items since there were no meshes provided for it which otherwise would have resulted into an invisible item
    * Changed the armor rating of the items to 0
    * Labia rings now use the same slot as the belts from Devious Devices
    * Nipple rings now use the same slot as the bra from Devious Devices
    * Navel piercings do now use Body Addon 6 as their primary slot (Biped Slot 47)
    * Doubled the weight of the items (from 0.025 to 0.05) and adjusted the base gold value slightly (Might be revisited)
    * Removed the temper recipes because they don't provide armor anymore
    * Removed the ArmorLight keyword
    * Added the JewelryExpensive keyword for items with base gold value over 250
    * Added the SexLabNoStrip keyword to all items


Installing MiC
Install my mod after you have installed the previous mods you want to use. Tick the options you want to have installed.


Credits
Calyps for creating the toys
Foaman for creating Calypsia - The Adult Toys Merchant
Shazar for creating SED7 Accessoire Piercingset


Changelog
    * 1.2
    - Removed Remodeled Armor because the newest version do not have panties anymore
    - Added Calypsia - The Adult Toy Merchant
    * 1.1.2
    - Switched to an All-in-1-Installer thanks to CG!, it includes the english version as well as the german version
    * 1.1.1
    - Accidentially marked the navel piercing as nipple piercings in SED7 Accessoires Piercingset - fixed
    * 1.1
    - SED7 Accessoire Piercingset added
    * 1.0
    - Initial Release</Description>
	<Website>http://www.loverslab.com/topic/24830-mic-make-it-compatible/</Website>
	<Groups>
		<element>Clothing and Equipment</element>
	</Groups>
</fomod>
